<testimonials>
	<quote>
		<statement>"Norwood Landscape's excellent work and customer service has been the single most important factor in helping us maintain a high level of curb appeal throughout our real estate portfolio."</statement>
		<author>Lucas C. ~ BAMSI, Brockton, Massachusetts</author>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<statement>"Norwood Lanscape's service over the years has been exceptional. It's a relief to know that our property always looks terrific."</statement>
		<author>Lees Y. ~ Brockton, Massachusetts</author>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<statement>"We here at BAMSI are especially pleased with Norwood Landscape's professionalism, courteousness, and high level of customer satisfaction. They are now our primary landscaping contractor maintaining over 40 of our commercial and residential properties."</statement>
		<author>Lucas C. ~ BAMSI, Brockton, Massachusetts</author>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<statement>"We have had the pleasure to work with Norwood Landscape for over 25 years and could not be more impressed and delighted with our experience."</statement>
		<author>Chris and Sue C., N. Easton, Massachusetts</author>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<statement>"Norwood Landscape Company has maintained many of our properties over the years. They provide us with the highest quality of service year round. No job is too big or too small and if I ever have a question, they respond in record time."</statement>
		<author>Cindy B., Brockton, Massachusetts</author>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<statement>"Many thanks to you and your crew for making my yard the most beautiful in East Bridgewater!"</statement>
		<author>Rosemary, East Bridgewater, Massachusetts</author>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<statement>"Norwood Landscaping maintains our yard and irrigation system with an attention to detail that other services were unable to achieve.  They are easy to contact and always responsive to our special requests. They arrive each week with a courteous, experienced team ready to exceed our expectations. It is our pleasure to highly recommend Norwood Landscaping."</statement>
		<author>Don and Pam S, Brockton, Massachusetts</author>
	</quote>
</testimonials>